jenkatgames.com 2014-11-21

# Privacy Policy at JenkatGames.com

Last Updated April 28, 2014

We have created this Privacy Policy in order to show our commitment to your privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices. This policy covers all Jenkat Media, Inc. properties including, but not limited to the following domains: http://www.jenkatmedia.com, http://www.jenkatgames.com,http://www.gamehug.com, Jenkat Games Arcade and Jenkat Games Arcade Plus, and all other websites and products owned and/or operated by Jenkat Media, Inc. (\\\\\"the Network\\\\\").

### PERSONAL INFORMATION

Any personal information that you provide to our Jenkat Media website(s) will stay safe and secure. 

### INFORMATION THAT WE MAY COLLECT FROM OUR USERS

We may collect the following information when you sign up for a service: 

  *   \- First name, last name, e-mail, postal address, country, phone number, gender, birth date, age, username, zip code, password, and game category preferences. 
  *   \- For processing transactions, we also collect either credit card information or bank information, depending on your form of payment. 

### IP Address:

When a user visits any website owned or operated by Jenkat Media, Inc., we may collect the IP address that requested the display of one of our sites. This address is collected primarily for two purposes. The first purpose is to exercise our ability to restrict access to the site by users who have violated our Terms of Service. The second purpose is to support our advertising partners, so that the partners will be able to accurately count the number of unique visitors to our sites who may have viewed a given advertisement. When a user accesses a Network website, our web server may also automatically collect and store the user\\\\\'s domain name, the date and time of access to the site and the Internet address of the website that linked you to our site.

### Sign Up and Survey information:

Any information you provide to us as part of your use of any Jenkat Media website will be stored as entered. 

### Cookies:

The sole purpose of cookies is to enhance your online experience. Cookies are small data files that are stored on your computer by websites. Through your Web browser, cookies are only used by the website that wrote the cookie. Data stored in a cookie from Jenkat Media is only accessible by the Jenkat Media websites. Data in cookies may be read to authenticate user sessions or provide services. The information in our cookies is kept private and secure. 

### USE OF COLLECTED INFORMATION

Your username, e-mail address, and password will be used to uniquely identify you as a user on any Jenkat Media website. We may use or display your username for such purposes including, but not limited to, rankings, competitions, lottery winnings, chat identification, or game high scores. 

Other identifying information collected during the sign up process or through other voluntary means (e.g., via surveys) may be used to calculate aggregate demographics figures.

We use the information that we collect from users in a variety of ways, including to improve the content of the website, to address user preferences and to attract new users, to track user trends and patterns on the Internet so that users may be informed about products and services of interest and, in some instances, to properly credit third parties that have referred users to the site. Stored information is also used to pre-populate information fields for purchases, contests or promotions.

Our advertisers and marketing partners who contract directly with the Network are required to confirm that they will comply with the Network\\\\\'s Privacy Policy with respect to information collected through ads displayed on any Network site. Third-party advertising companies use cookies to measure and improve the effectiveness of their clients\\\\\' ads. To do this, advertisers may use anonymous information about a user\\\\\'s visit to a website (as well as other websites) including what banner ad was shown, the date and time it was shown, the cookie and the IP address. This information may also be used for online preference marketing purposes. The Network does not control these third party cookies and users of the Network should check the privacy policy of the advertising company or advertiser to see whether and how it uses cookies. 

A pixel tag is a tiny image inserted in a webpage and used to record the number and types of views for that page. The Network may allow third party pixel tags to be present on the Network for purposes of advertising, providing services or data and statistics collection. You can program your computer to warn you each time a cookie is being sent, block third party cookies or block all cookies. However, by blocking all cookies you may not have access to certain features on the Network. Visit Network Advertising Initiative\\\\\'s (\\\\\"NAI\\\\\") gateway opt-out site www.networkadvertising.org to review the privacy policies of third-party advertising companies and/or opt-out of third-party advertising cookies. 

In the event that Jenkat Media, Inc. merges with another company or transfers or sells substantially all of its assets to a third party, all information stored on the web server would be included in the merger, transfer or sale. Also, if required by law, information may be disclosed to a third party. 

Jenkat Media, Inc. reserves the right to change its privacy policy at any time. 

### SECURITY OF COLLECTED INFORMATION

All data that we collect is stored on one or more secure database servers that cannot be accessed from outside our corporate network. Outside of our network, the only access to this data is that provided through our Jenkat Media websites. Through our sites, access to personal information is completely controlled by user-defined e-mail addresses and passwords. Within our corporation, access to data is secured through a private user ID and password known only to key personnel who maintain the database. 

Except as described in this Privacy Policy, the Network will get your permission before we use any personally identifiable information you provide to us in a way that is inconsistent with the purpose for which it was submitted or share your personally identifiable information with third parties that are not affiliated with the Network. 

### E-MAIL/OPT-OUT

When you sign up as a Jenkat Media user, or download any software from Jenkat Media, Inc., by default the option will be selected to allow us to communicate with you via e-mail about news, games, special offers, and events. You have the option to uncheck or check a box during the sign up process that will prevent this, although by doing so you are potentially asking us to not inform you of events and prize awards that may have tangible value to you. Any e-mail we send to you will contain information about opting-out of any further mailings, and all Jenkat Media websites have areas where you may manually opt-out of receiving further communications. Jenkat Media treats each of its consumer offerings individually, so if you have opted to receive mailings from more than one business entity, if you want to unsubscribe you must do so from each entity individually. 

A second communication option is chosen by default, allowing Jenkat Media to share your information with trusted partners who may also choose to communicate with you. You also have the choice to uncheck the box for this option during the sign up process.

### CHILDREN\'S PRIVACY

Jenkat Games is not intended for use by anyone under the age of 13. Jenkat Games does not permit the registration on the Sites by, and will not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from, anyone under 13 years of age.  In the event that we learn that we have inadvertently gathered personal information from children under the age of 13, we will take reasonable measures to promptly erase such information from our records.

### FACEBOOK PLATFORM

This site makes use of Facebook Platform which lets you log into other applications and websites using your Facebook account. When you log in using Facebook, Facebook gives Jenkat Media your User ID, but they do not share your email address or password with Jenkat Media without you giving permission.  

If you already have an account with Jenkat Media, you may also be able to connect that account with your Facebook account. This can be done using techniques like an \\\\\"email hash\\\\\", which is similar to searching for someone on Facebook using an email address. The email addresses in this case are encrypted, so no email addresses are actually shared between Facebook and Jenkat Media.  

How It Works  

The website (Jenkat Media) sends over an encrypted version of your email address, and Facebook matches it with a database of email addresses that they have also encrypted. If there is a match, then Facebook tells the website the User ID associated with the email address. This way, when you log into our website using Facebook, we can link your Facebook account to your account on Jenkat Media.

About Social Plugins  

When you go to a game or application, or connect with a website using the Facebook Platform, Facebook gives the game, application, or website (sometimes referred to as just \\\\\"Applications\\\\\" or \\\\\"Apps\\\\\") your _User ID_ , as well your friends\\\\\' User IDs (or your friend list).

Your friend list helps us make your experience more social because it lets you find your friends on our website. Your User ID helps us personalize your experience because it can connect your account on our website with your Facebook account, and it can access your _public information_. This includes the information you choose to make public, as well as information that is always publicly available. If the application needs additional information, it will have to ask you for specific permission.  

The _Apps you Use_ setting in Facebook lets you control the applications you use. You can see the permissions you have given these applications, as well as the last time an application accessed your information. You can also remove applications you no longer want, or turn off all Facebook applications.  

Jenkat Media might also ask for permission to share specific information with the games and applications you use on our site (such as your public information). If you say okay, we will not be able to access any other information about you without asking specific permission from you or your friends.  

### OTHER INFORMATION COLLECTED

Your Web browser or client software that you use to access Jenkat Media may transmit certain geographic information and information regarding the capabilities or features of your computer and/or software to us. We may also track other types of information, such as what games a user plays, how long our users have been members of any Jenkat Media businesses or programs, the last time a user visited Jenkat Media websites, and whether a user has won any of our games, lotteries, jackpots, or contests. We may use this information to calculate aggregate statistics about our user community or for security purposes, and may provide such information to advertisers and/or partners in aggregate form only. 

Within certain games available on the website, your Windows Account Name may be used to populate your profile within the software program.  

### HOW INFORMATION IS USED

The information you provide to Jenkat Media will allow us to notify you about new features, enhancements, resolution of site problems, handle and/or route your customer support questions and issues, and inform you of upgrade opportunities, contests, prizes, or special events. Jenkat Media may use personal information in combination with data from third parties for similar purposes as well. 

### THIRD-PARTY ADVERTISING

It is important that you understand that advertisers or websites that link to a Jenkat Media website may collect personal information about you. The Privacy Policy does not apply to, and cannot control the activities of, other advertisers or websites. We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads on our sites. These companies may use information about your visits to this and other sites in order to help them provide relevant ads to users. 

### SHARING INFORMATION

Jenkat Media may disclose your personal information to third-party vendors to fulfill prizes in those instances in which we do not provide prize fulfillment directly. We may also use your information to process our newsletters or e-mail campaigns, or to analyze and/or store data. Under some limited and special circumstances, we may also disclose your information if there is a violation of the Terms of Service or if we have a good faith belief that the law requires it. It is important that you understand that we cannot control the activities of such third-party vendors. While we cannot guarantee that they will adhere to the same privacy and security procedures as Jenkat Media, we will take all reasonable precautions under the circumstances to ensure the protection of your personal information. 

### CHAT & MESSAGING

Jenkat Media websites may choose to operate message boards and/or chat areas where users can exchange ideas and communicate with one another. When posting to a message board or chat area, it is important for you to understand that the information is being made publicly available in an online environment. Any information posted is the sole responsibility of the individual user. 

### Are you concerned about our use of personal information?

If, for any reason, you are concerned with the way that we may be using your personal information, you may request that we cease to use your information or you may file a complaint by contacting Jenkat Media, Inc., Privacy Policy Department, P.O. Box 68, Lake Elmo, MN 55042.

### AGREEMENT WITH JENKAT MEDIA POLICIES

By using any of the Jenkat Media websites, products, or services, you signify your understanding and agreement to the Privacy Policy stated here, and to the Terms of Service. If you do not agree with our policies, please do not use any of the Jenkat Media websites, products, or services.
